function getData() {
    return [
        {
            question: "What character should be used to separate multiple values for an EditText's android:inputType?",
            options: ["@", "comma", "#", "|"],
            correct: "|"
        },
        {
           question: "If a visual control had a property/value of android:paddingLeft=\"@dimen/activity_horizontal_margin\", you would expect the value to come from the dimens.xml resource file.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "Lollipop works on devices with 64-bit ARM, Intel and MIPS processors.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "All image file names must contain only lowercase letters.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "Android screen designs can be categorized by",
           options: ["screen size and density of the device", "the screen size of the device", "the screen shape of the device"],
           correct: "screen size and density of the device"
        },
        {
           question: "Using overridePendingTransition(), two custom-built transitions can be explicitly applied to the entering and exiting activities.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "Kitkat is optimized to run with a minimum of 128MB of Ram.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "A _____ is a specialized control that is optimized for displaying long lists of items.",
           options: ["ListView", "Scroller", "MasterList", "all of these"],
           correct: "ListView"
        },
        {
           question: "The mechanism for delivering an Intent to an activity is sendActivity().",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "What type of file is used to specify the app's user interface components using XML?",
           options: ["values file", "layout file", "activity file", "interface file"],
           correct: "layout file"
        },
        {
           question: "Developers can only sign an application in release mode.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "When an Activity has been paused, due to a previous activity being resumed, the ___ callback method is called.",
           options: ["onCreate()", "onResume()", "onPause()", "onStart()"],
           correct: "onPause()"
        },
        {
           question: "What Activity method is called once the activity has been created and becomes visible to the user?",
           options: ["onStart()", "onRestart()", "onCreate()", "onResume()"],
           correct: "onStart()"
        },
        {
           question: "A Fragment is integrated into an Activity, but does not need an Activity to run.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "In Android API level 14 and above, you can add an attribute to the AndroidManifest.xml file to split the Action Bar into a top and bottom action bar.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "Which layout type would typically be used to arrange UI elements vertically side-by-side?",
           options: ["LinearLayout", "RelativeLayout", "GridLayout", "TableLayout"],
           correct: "LinearLayout"
        },
        {
           question: "Developers typically construct a single XML layout file for each Activity class in an app.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "The activity's onDestroy() method is a good place to stop actions that consume a noticeable amount of CPU in order to make the switch to the next activity as fast as possible.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "A Service can be used to handle network transactions.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "Animation resource files are defined using XML code.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "Android discourages the separation of functionality and resources.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "The file _____ contains the unique identifiers for drawables, strings, layout elements and other resources.",
           options: ["gradle", "AndroidManifest.xml", "R.java"],
           correct: "R.java"
        },
        {
           question: "The advantage of building applications that use Fragments is their ability to easily present a consistently well-designed user interface.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "For the user to begin interacting with the application Activity, the ___ callback method is called.",
           options: ["onResume()", "onCreate()", "onStart()", "onPause()"],
           correct: "onResume()"
        },
        {
           question: "Developers only need to provide a single image for each drawable resource since Android will automatically ensure the images look good on a variety of screen densities.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "Fragments can be used without an activity.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "An Android app's user interface can be created from Java code.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "How are fragments typically used when implementing the master/detail flow interface design pattern on a tablet-sized Android device?",
           options: ["Fragments are not typically used with the master/detail design pattern.", 
            "Two activities each use two different fragments to display the master and detail screens.",
            "A single activity uses the same fragment to display both the master and detail panels.",
            "A single activity uses one fragment to display the master panel and one to display the detail panel." ],
           correct: "A single activity uses one fragment to display the master panel and one to display the detail panel."
        },
        {
           question: "The ____ callback is a good place to stop actions that consume a noticeable amount of CPU in order to make the switch to the next Activity as fast as possible.",
           options: ["onPause()", "onResume()", "onStop()", "onStart()"],
           correct: "onPause()"
        },
        {
           question: "The final Android application is packaged into a(n)",
           options: ["pkg file.", "apk file.", "apf file."],
           correct: "apk file."
        },
        {
           question: "String value resources are implemented as XML files.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "What is the action overflow menu used for?",
           options: ["Holding less frequently used actions.", 
            "Holding actions that do not fit on the action bar and Holding less frequently used actions.",
            "Holding buttons purely related to navigation.", 
            "Holding actions that do not fit on the action bar."],
           correct: "Holding actions that do not fit on the action bar and Holding less frequently used actions."
        },
        {
           question: "The TextWatcher can be used with an EditText to determine when the user changes focus to or from the EditText control.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "Java programs are compiled into ________ which are interpreted and executed by a Java virtual machine.",
           options: ["JRE", "machine code", "bytecode", "Dalvik"],
           correct: "bytecode"
        },
        {
           question: "The Key Store creates a certificate with a private key and a password.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "The main purpose of a GridLayout is to display tabular data when there is a significant amount of data for the user to navigate by scrolling.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "The _____ is a development tool that can capture screenshots, record video, and provide state information of an application currently running.",
           options: ["MDS", "ADT", "DDMS"],
           correct: "DDMS"
        },
        {
           question: "What EditText property can be used to produce a soft keyboard with a search icon?",
           options: ["android:inputType", "android:searchIcon", "android:imeOptions", "android:gravity"],
           correct: "android:imeOptions"
        },
        {
           question: "The onStart() callback method is always called after onRestart().",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "All Android applications are composed of at least two Activity classes.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "An Android app cannot be debugged if it is running on a physical device.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "Dalvik is the default of Lollipop.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "Designing an outstanding Android application involves considerable thought and analysis of usability and user interface design.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "Which of these types of data is a Bundle not capable of storing?",
           options: ["char", "Parcelable object", "byte", "All of these can be stored in a Bundle."],
           correct: "All of these can be stored in a Bundle."
        },
        {
           question: "You need to modify the R.java file when you need a new identifier for your controls.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "What component represented the Model in the Tap Button Counter app?",
           options: ["MainActivity class", "main_layout.xml", "TextView class", "Counter class"],
           correct: "Counter class"
        },
        {
           question: "The Fragment's onCreateView() method is typically used to restore the fragment's state.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "Honeycomb was designed to support tablets.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "An interpolator can be used in a transition animation in order to accelerate or decelerate a translation.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "A fragment may only be used in one screen within an application.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "What method is used to load and inflate an Activity's layout file?",
           options: ["setContentView", "loadInterface", "onCreate", "loadLayoutFile"],
           correct: "setContentView"
        },
        {
           question: "When using Adaptive Design for designing the UI, the developer can create four different layout XML files to target four different general sizes of Android devices.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "An activity can determine if it needs to show the master and detail panes on the same screen or launch a second activity that displays the detail alone by doing what?",
           options: ["Checking the width and height of the device.", 
            "Checking to see if the proper settings exist in AndroidManifest.xml.",
            "Checking to see if the system is currently displaying a layout with two panes or a single pane.",
            "Checking to see if the device supports fragments."],
           correct: "Checking to see if the system is currently displaying a layout with two panes or a single pane."
        },
        {
           question: "Android applications use C++.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "The Action Bar can display drop-down menus.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "What defines the characteristics of the device an application will be tested on using the Android Emulator?",
           options: ["JDK", "Android SDK", "AVD", "Gradle"],
           correct: "AVD"
        },
        {
           question: "The ListView obtains data to display from what?",
           options: ["AndroidManifest.xml", "An array of strings", "An Adapter", "strings.xml"],
           correct: "An Adapter"
        },
        {
           question: "The XML layout file used for landscape orientation should be placed in what directory?",
           options: ["res/layout", "layout/land", "res/layout-land", "res/landscape"],
           correct: "res/layout-land"
        },
        {
           question: "Rather than simply using an Activity and a Layout to define the complete user interface of an application screen, it is often more efficient to use fragments.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "Android will save the state of an activity when it is paused or stopped, but the state is not automatically saved if the activity is destroyed.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "The ___ callback method is called when an Activity is no longer visible to the user.",
           options: ["onStop()", "onPause()", "onResume()", "onStart()"],
           correct: "onStop()"
        },
        {
           question: "An Android Activity is represented as a Controller object in the Model-View-Controller architecture.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "A(n) _____ is used for screen designs that require control elements to be positioned in relation to one another.",
           options: ["TableLayout", "LinearLayout", "RelativeLayout"],
           correct: "RelativeLayout"
        },
        {
           question: "Table cells can span multiple columns when using a TableLayout, but they cannot span multiple rows.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "What happens to Action buttons using android:showAsAction=\"ifRoom\" that cannot fit on the action bar due to constraints in size?",
           options: ["They are placed in the action overflow menu.", "All the Action buttons are shrunk so they all fit.", 
            "The application will not run if there are too many Action buttons that cannot all fit.", "They are simply not displayed."],
           correct: "They are placed in the action overflow menu."
        },
        {
           question: "A(n) _____ is called to when the running fragment is no longer interacting with the user.",
           options: ["onResume()", "onStart()", "onPause()"],
           correct: "onPause()"
        },
        {
           question: "An implicit Intent is typically used to start up a named target activity.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "An action bar can feature",
           options: ["user action control elements", "drop-down menus", "navigation modes", "all of these"],
           correct: "all of these"
        },
        {
           question: "Android recommends the use of graphics that are interlaced.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "When an activity needs to extract data from the intent that started it, it examines the onCreate() method's Bundle parameter.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "There is no Java virtual machine in the Android platform.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "What Fragment method is called when the fragment is no longer visible to the user?",
           options: ["onPause", "onDestroy", "onDetatch", "onStop"],
           correct: "onStop"
        },
        {
           question: "Cutout prototypes can serve as micro experiments to explore strengths and weaknesses of tactile handling of an Android app.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "Which of these controls is used to select a single item from a list of items that displays in a dropdown menu when the control is selected?",
           options: ["RadioButton", "Switch", "SeekBar", "Spinner"],
           correct: "Spinner"
        },
        {
           question: "It is common to populate an AdapterView by binding it directly to an array.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "The OnCheckedChangeListener interface can be used to determine if the user has selected a check box or a radio button.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "All the Activities that compose an Android app must be declared in what file?",
           options: ["AndroidManifest.xml", "strings.xml", "build.gradle", "activities.xml"],
           correct: "AndroidManifest.xml"
        },
        {
           question: "The following code segment shows a(n) _______ Intent.<br/>Intent intent = new Intent(getApplicationContext(), TargetActivity.class);<br/>startActivity(intent);",
           options: ["Implicit", "Abstract", "Explicit"],
           correct: "Explicit"
        },
        {
           question: "Transition animations can be applied directly to fragments.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "A fragment using an animation with “rotationX” would make the fragment rotate around an imaginary line that runs horizontally across the screen.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "Android developers must create new keys to sign their apps whenever they make updates to their app.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "Once the soft keyboard is visible, it should not be programmatically hidden.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "Animation resource files are typically stored in a directory called anim.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "Which of the following is not a Container View?",
           options: ["ListView", "RadioGroup", "HorizontalScrollView", "TableLayout"],
           correct: "TableLayout"
        },
        {
           question: "An activity that used overridePendingTransition() in its onStart() method to load a <translate> animation with fromXDelta=\"0\" and toXDelta=\"-100%\" would move the activity's layout to the right and completely off the screen when it transitions to another activity.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "It is recommended that Android developers use an integrated development environment (IDE) to build Android applications.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "Which Container Group is used to display a vertically scrolling list of items that when selected can expand to show the selected item's child Views?",
           options: ["ScrollView", "ExpandableListView", "GridView", "ListView"],
           correct: "ExpandableListView"
        },
        {
           question: "Once an Activity has been paused and a new activity comes into focus, the ___ callback method is called.",
           options: ["onResume()", "onPause()", "onStart()", "onStop()"],
           correct: "onStop()"
        },
        {
           question: "A(n) _____ is called when the fragment is no longer visible to the user either because its activity is being stopped or a fragment operation is modifying it in the activity.",
           options: ["onDestroy", "onPause()", "onStop()"],
           correct: "onStop()"
        },
        {
           question: "A FrameLayout can be defined within XML layout resources, but it is often created programmatically in the app's Java code.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "An Android app can be configured to have no title bar and fill the entire screen by specifying the android:theme in what file?",
           options: ["MainActivity.java", "strings.xml", "AndroidManifest.xml", "activity_main.xml"],
           correct: "AndroidManifest.xml"
        },
        {
           question: "View objects are invisible view containers that define how child views are load out, such as in a grid or vertical list.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "A Fragment uses the lifecycle of the associated Activity.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "All animations in a <set> are always played together at the same time.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "A(n) _____ is used to arrange layout elements into tabular rows and columns.",
           options: ["TableLayout", "LinearLayout", "RelativeLayout"],
           correct: "TableLayout"
        },
        {
           question: "The onPause() calledback methid is called as part of the Activity lifecycle when an Activity is moving into the background, but has not been destroyed.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "Setting the android:inputType to “textEmailAddress” makes the soft keyboard show the @ symbol prominently.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "	_____ is an edit operation that can occur in a fragment transaction.",
           options: ["add()", "attach()", "hide()", "all of these"],
           correct: "all of these"
        },
        {
           question: "An activity's state may be restored in either onCreate() or onRestoreInstanceState().",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "Actions such as transition animations and access to required devices, such as the camera, are often initiated within the ____ method.",
           options: ["onCreate()", "onPause()", "onResume()", "onStart()"],
           correct: "onResume()"
        },
        {
           question: "Logging reports can have a negative impact on the performance of an application.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "ART is designed to be fully compatible with Dalvik's existing bytecode format.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "Developers only need to ensure that their applications run on the most recent version of Android.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "Although an activity may require text input when the activity starts, there is no way to get the soft keyboard to appear automatically when the activity first starts.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "What project file specifies the hardware requirements of an Android application?",
           options: ["AndroidManifest.xml", "build.gradle", "strings.xml", "MainActivity.java"],
           correct: "AndroidManifest.xml"
        },
        {
           question: "A density-independent pixel (dp) is a virtual pixel unit that is equivalent to one physical pixel on a",
           options: ["260 dpi screen.", "60 dpi screen.", "160 dpi screen."],
           correct: "160 dpi screen."
        },
        {
           question: "Every application has one Activity class that serves as the main Activity.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "The method setCustomAnimations(int enter, int exit) is used to play an animation for enter and exit operations on a fragment, but these animations will not be played when popping the back stack.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "Every visual control object in an Android user interface is a subclass of android.view.View.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "What Android widget can be used to toggle something on and off?",
           options: ["CheckBox", "Switch", "ToggleButton", "All the above"],
           correct: "All the above"
        },
        {
           question: "An application's build files are stored in the",
           options: ["Gradle Scripts directory.", "manifest directory.", "java directory."],
           correct: "Gradle Scripts directory."
        },
        {
           question: "A(n) _____ is called immediately prior to the fragment no longer being associated with its activity.",
           options: ["onDestroy()", "onStop()", "onDetach()"],
           correct: "onDetach()"
        },
        {
           question: "When an Activity has been created and becomes visible to the user, the ____ callback method is called.",
           options: ["onResume()", "onStart()", "onCreate()", "onPause()"],
           correct: "onStart()"
        },
        {
           question: "Usually the layouts for fragments used by an activity are all stored in a single layout file.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "What was the first version of Android that was specifically implemented for tablets?",
           options: ["Honeycomb", "KitKat", "Ice Cream Sandwich", "Gingerbread"],
           correct: "Honeycomb"
        },
        {
           question: "An Android emulator mimics only the software features of a typical mobile device.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "Fragments are particularly helpful in adapting a user experience across a wide range of devices.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "The action bar button icons can be custom-build or borrowed from android.R.drawable.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "A fragment restores its state by adding logic to what lifecycle callback?",
           options: ["OnResume", "Fragments do not need to save or restore their state.", "OnCreate", "OnRestoreState"],
           correct: "OnCreate"
        },
        {
           question: "Intents are used to start up which of these components?",
           options: ["Activities", "Broadcast receivers", "Services", "All of these"],
           correct: "All of these"
        },
        {
           question: "Warning level errors are recoverable error-type logs that do not produce data loss.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "A(n) _____ is called at the start of a fragment lifecycle.",
           options: ["onStart()", "onPause()", "onResume()"],
           correct: "onStart()"
        },
        {
           question: "The View layout XML used by a ListView must be defined inside the same XML file as the &lt;ListView&gt;.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "When the user long-presses an Action button's icon, a tool-tip containing the button's title will display.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "If an implicit Intent were used to start an activity using Intent.ACTION_SEND, any activity with a matching ACTION_SEND <intent-filter> could potentially be started.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "What method is used to add data to an Intent?",
           options: ["setAction()", "addData()", "You cannot add data to an Intent.", "putExtra()"],
           correct: "putExtra()"
        },
        {
           question: "The findViewById() function is supplied the identifier from R.java for the control to locate.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "A scene contains various property/values of a View hierarchy that are animated when the scene enters or leaves the View hierarchy.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        },
        {
           question: "Responsive design is primarily used for the rearrangement of fixed user interface elements in an application.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "False"
        },
        {
           question: "Information cannot be passed between Activities in an application.",
           options: ["True", "False"],
           correct: "True"
        }
    ];
}